we've seen in the past that the VCG
我们过去曾看到VCG
mechanism gives rise to dominant
机制引起主导
strategies and efficient allocations we
策略和有效分配
know that in general it doesn't give
知道一般来说，它不会给
rise to individual rationality or budget
提高个人理性或预算
balance in this video we'll see that
在这部影片中保持平衡，我们将看到
under some pretty mild additional
在一些相当温和的附加条件下
assumptions it is possible for us to get
假设我们有可能得到
both of these things now remember that
这两个东西现在都记得
individual rationality means that it
个人理性意味着
makes sense for agents to participate in
代理商参与是有意义的
a mechanism if they had a choice between
一种机制，如果他们可以选择
participating and not participating they
参与而不参与
would be happy to participate and recall
乐于参与和回忆
that budget balance means that it
预算余额意味着
doesn't cost money to run the mechanism
运行该机制无需花费金钱
that the mechanism either keeps
该机制要么保持
completely breaks even all the time
一直保持完全收支平衡
which we've already seen in the previous
我们已经在之前的内容中看到了
video is impossible for VCG or at least
VCG或至少无法播放视频
his weekly budget balance at least turns
他的每周预算余额至少达到
a profit or or breaks even and what
利润或盈亏平衡以及什么
we'll see in this video is that we can
我们将在此视频中看到，我们可以
have both of these two properties so let
具有这两个属性，所以让
me start with individual rationality to
我从个人理性开始
get individual rationality I'm going to
得到我要去的个人理性
need two different assumptions to be
需要两个不同的假设
true of the environment the first is
对环境的真实性首先是
called choice set monotonicity and this
称为选择集单调性
assumption says that for all agents the
假设表明，对于所有代理商
set of outcomes that are achievable
可实现的一组结果
without that agent present is a weak
没有那个代理人是一个弱者
subset of the set of eight of the set of
一组的八个的子集
outcomes that are possible when that
当那可能的结果
agent is present so in other words when
代理存在，换句话说，当
I remove an agent from the mechanism as
我从机制中删除代理
of course I have to do inside the
当然我必须在里面做
payment evaluation for VCG the mechanism
VCG支付评估机制
set of choices that are available to it
可用的一组选择
weekly goes down so no in particular no
每周下降，所以没有特别没有
new choices become possible when
当出现新的选择时
somebody gets removed the second
有人被删除第二
assumption that I'll make is called no
我会做的假设称为否
negative externalities and I'll say that
负面的外部性，我会说
we have no negative externalities if for
如果没有，我们没有负面的外部性
all agents and all choices that can be
所有代理商和所有可能的选择
made without that agent the agents own
在没有代理人的情况下制作的
valuation for each of these choices is
这些选择的估值为
non negative so in other words when you
非负面的，换句话说，当你
get dropped from the mechanism it isn't
从不是的机制中脱颖而出
possible for the mechanism to choose
机制可能选择
something that actually causes you pain
真正让你痛苦的东西
you might it might
你可能会
choose something that you like less well
选择不太喜欢的东西
than what it chooses when you are
比当你选择的时候
present but it can't choose something
目前，但无法选择
for which you have negative utility
对于您有负面效用
let's look at two examples of realistic
让我们看两个现实的例子
scenarios that that satisfy both of
同时满足以下两个条件的方案
these properties to give you a sense of
这些属性给您一种感觉
why these properties are reasonable to
为什么这些属性对
assume so the first is the road-building
假设所以首先是修路
referendum problem so consider this
公投问题，请考虑一下
problem where we want to have a vote
我们想投票的问题
between agents to decide whether or not
代理商之间决定是否
to build a public good like a road so
像道路一样建设公共物品
the set of choices has nothing to do
选择集无关
with the number of agents because the
与代理商的数量，因为
two choices are that either the road
两种选择是，要么
gets built or the road doesn't get built
被修筑或道路未被修筑
remember that the payments come from the
请记住，付款来自
payment function those aren't the
支付功能不是
choices and so the choice set is
选择，所以选择集是
monotonic it's monotonic in the weak
单调的，在弱者中是单调的
sense that it just doesn't change with
感觉它不会随着
the number of agents but remember that
代理商人数，但请记住
we allowed for a weak subset secondly
其次，我们考虑了一个弱子集
let's assume that no agent negatively
假设没有代理商负面影响
values the project so some agents might
重视项目，以便某些代理商可能
like it better for the the road not to
喜欢它更好的道路不
be built than for the road to be built
建造比建造道路
but let's say that none of the agents
但是，假设没有代理商
experiences negative utility in any
在任何情况下都具有负面效用
situation that still seems like a
情况似乎仍然像
reasonable model of this problem and
这个问题的合理模型
that would give us no negative
那不会给我们带来负面影响
externalities okay well we saw an
外部性好吧，我们看到了
example previously where Troy said
特洛伊说过的例子
monotonicity
单调性
arose in a pretty trivial way because
以非常琐碎的方式出现，因为
the set of choices just didn't change
选择的集合只是没有改变
let's look at a richer example where the
让我们看一个更丰富的例子
set of choices does change so here let's
选择的集合确实会发生变化，所以让我们
think about kind of a simplified stock
考虑一种简化的库存
market in which we have two different
我们有两个不同的市场
kinds of agents some of them have a
某些代理商，其中一些有
single unit of a stock that they want to
他们想要的股票的单个单位
sell so they have one share of Apple
出售，因此他们拥有一股苹果
stock and they want to sell it we have
股票，他们想卖掉我们有
another group of agents who want to buy
另一组想要购买的代理商
one share of Apple stock and we have
一股苹果股票，我们有
some number of agents on both sides of
双方都有一定数量的代理商
the market now the choices that the
现在市场的选择
mechanism can make here are different
机制可以使这里有所不同
ways of pairing together buyers and
将买家配对在一起的方式，以及
sellers so every buyer can interact with
卖家，以便每个买家都可以与
only one seller every seller can
每个卖家只能有一个卖家
interact with only one buyer and nobody
只与一位买家互动，没人
has to interact so the pairing where
必须互动，所以配对在哪里
nobody gets paired is valid the pairing
没有人配对是有效的配对
were just two people get paired is Val
只有两个人配对是Val
and Paran wear as many people as
波兰人穿的人多达
possible get paired is valid so we have
可能配对是有效的，所以我们有
these various different ways of
这些各种不同的方式
establishing trades that might happen in
建立可能发生的交易
this market now think about what happens
现在这个市场思考发生了什么
if I add a new agent to the market
如果我向市场添加新代理商
none of the pairings that worked when
没有配对有效
that agent wasn't present go away when I
当我不存在那个特工
add a new person they're all still
添加一个新的人，他们仍然
possible to do because I could always
可以做，因为我总是
just set that new person aside but I can
只是把那个新人放在一边，但我可以
also have that new person participate in
也有新人参加
trades that weren't possible without
没有这些就不可能进行的交易
that person there and thus you can see
那个人在那里，你可以看到
here that choice set monotonicity is
这里选择集的单调性是
satisfied in a more interesting way
以更有趣的方式满意
because new options become available
因为有了新的选择
when I add an agent but no old options
当我添加代理但没有旧选​​项时
get ruled out and it's natural in this
被排除在外，这很自然
kind of a setting to assume that agents
一种假设代理人的设置
have zero utility both for other people
他人的效用均为零
trading with each other and for other
彼此进行交易
people not trading at all and that being
人们根本不交易，那是
the case the agent has zero utility for
代理的效用为零的情况
everything that can happen when they're
当他们
not present and so there are no negative
不存在，所以没有负面影响
externalities so now we're ready to
外部性，所以我们现在准备
consider the main result that we want to
考虑我们想要的主要结果
establish for this part of the video
为视频的这一部分建立
which is that these two assumptions that
这是这两个假设
we've just made of choice set
我们刚刚选择了一套
monotonicity and no- no- externalities
单调性和非外部性
are sufficient to make the VCG mechanism
足以使VCG机制
ex-post individual rational now let's
现在事后个人理性
remember what ex-post individual
记得事后的个人
rational means as I said at the
正如我在
beginning of the video individual
视频个人的开头
rationality means that agents always
理性意味着代理商总是
have weakly positive utility for
对...的积极作用微弱
participating in the mechanism and
参与机制
ex-post means that this is true
事后意味着这是真的
regardless of what valuations any of the
不论任何估值
agents have so this is true for every
代理商有，所以每个人都这样
realization evaluations that the agent
代理商的实现评估
himself and also all of the other agents
他自己以及所有其他特工
might have so this is the strongest kind
可能有，所以这是最强的一种
of individual rationality so this is the
个人理性，所以这是
most desirable property about individual
关于个人的最理想的属性
rationality that we would hope to prove
我们希望证明的合理性
about VCG and that makes this an
关于VCG，这使得它成为
encouraging result so here's how we
令人鼓舞的结果，所以这就是我们
prove it we begin by saying
为了证明这一点，我们先说
that all of the agents truthfully
所有代理商都如实
declare their valuations in equilibrium
均衡宣布其估值
because we want to think about what
因为我们想考虑一下
happens in equilibrium and then we can
发生在平衡状态，然后我们可以
write this expression for agent i's
为代理商我写这个表达式
expected utility for participating in
参与的预期效用
the mechanism well he gets his value for
他很好地获得了价值的机制
the allocation that actually happens so
实际发生的分配
this is the choice that VCG actually
这是VCG实际上的选择
makes given that everybody reports their
考虑到每个人都报告他们的
values truthfully and he gets his value
真实地估价，他得到了价值
for that choice and then he pays the VCG
为此选择，然后他支付了VCG
payment function that we all know and
我们都知道的支付功能
love so because I've assumed that
爱，是因为我假设
everybody reports truthfully I don't
大家如实报道我不
have any V hats anywhere so I can
到处都有V帽，所以我可以
collect terms and particularly I can I
收集条款，特别是我可以
can roll this into one of the sums so I
可以将其汇总为一个总和，所以我
here get a sum over all of the agents
这里得到所有代理商的总和
minus a sum over all of the agents
减去所有代理商的总和
except for I now it comes the part where
除了我现在它来的部分
I use tri-set monotonicity so remember
我使用三集单调性，所以请记住
that this expression X of V is the
V的这个表达式X是
outcome that VCG chose which means that
VCG选择的结果，这意味着
it maximizes social welfare and by
它最大程度地提高了社会福利，
choice admonish Nyssa t this other
选择告诫尼莎其他
outcome X of V minus I was also one of
V的结果X减去我也是
the available choices when we when we
当我们何时我们可用的选择
picked this instead and so what that
取而代之的是什么
means is there must have been at least
意味着必须至少有
as much social welfare arising under
在此之下产生的社会福利
this choice as under this choice if not
如果没有，则将此选择视为该选择
the optimization would have just picked
优化本来就是
this one and so writing that as an
这样写，作为一个
equation the sum of agents values for
方程式的代理商价值总和
this choice is at least as big as the
这个选择至少与
sum of agents values for this choice I'm
我选择的代理商价值总和
just moving that equation up here and
只是将方程式移至此处
now I can also use no negative
现在我也可以不用负数
externalities let me just write the
外部性让我写
definition of no negative externalities
没有负面外部影响的定义
so the value that I has for the choice
所以我有选择的价值
that gets made when he's not present is
当他不在时被制造出来的是
greater than or equal to zero
大于或等于零
and what that means is that if I change
那意味着如果我改变
this expression here to J not equal to I
这里的这个表达式对J不等于I
then I've just taken out a non negative
那我就拿出一个非负数
number here which means
这里的数字意味着
this whole thing got smaller and that
这整个东西变小了
means the inequality still holds and so
意味着不平等仍然存在，所以
I have this expression here and that's
我在这里有这个表情
exactly what I wanted to prove because
正是我想证明的，因为
remember the ad agency utility is this
记住广告代理商实用工具是这个
expression and so I want to ensure that
表达，所以我想确保
this number is bigger than this number
这个数字大于这个数字
if it is then this whole thing is
如果是这样，那么整个事情就是
positive and I have individual
积极，我有个人
rationality and that's exactly what we
理性，这正是我们
just find here that this in fact is
只是在这里发现这实际上是
positive our non negative and so we do
正面我们的非负面，所以我们这样做
obtain an individual rationality okay so
获得个人理性好吧
much for individual rationality now I
现在对于个人理性我有很多
want to talk about budget balance so
想谈谈预算平衡
here's the property that we need at
这是我们需要的物业
trends at one property is enough for
一处物业的趋势足以满足
showing that VCG is weekly budget
显示VCG是每周预算
balanced and we call this no single
平衡的，我们称此为单身
agent effect so an environment exhibits
代理效应，因此环境表现出来
no single agent effect if it's the case
如果是这种情况，则没有单一代理的影响
that for all agents I all valuations of
对于所有代理商，我的所有估值
the agents other than I that are
除我以外的代理商
possible and all choices acts that
一切可能的选择
maximize the social welfare there exists
使存在的社会福利最大化
another choice X prime which is feasible
另一种可行的选择X素数
without I which means it's possible for
没有我，这意味着有可能
us to pick it even if I has been dropped
即使我掉线，我们也可以选择
and for which all of the agents other
以及所有其他代理商
than I get more social welfare than
比我得到的社会福利多
under the original allocation so in
根据原来的分配
other words if I drop an agent I and
换句话说，如果我放弃一个代理商，我和
then I pick some other choice instead
然后我选择其他选择
without I everybody other than I is at
没有我，没有其他人
least as happy with the new choice as
至少对新选择感到满意
with the old choice so the welfare of
与旧的选择，这样的福利
agents other than I is weakly increased
除我以外的其他代理人的增长微弱
when we drop I that might sound a little
当我们放下我时，听起来可能有点
confusing it's actually a really natural
混淆这实际上是很自然的
property here's an example think about a
属性，这是一个示例，请考虑
single-sided auction where for example I
单面拍卖，例如我
have one good for sale the choices in
有一个出售的选择
this case are all of the different
这种情况都是不同的
agents that could give the good two and
可以给好的两个和
if I drop an agent one of two things is
如果我放下代理商，两件事之一是
possible either that agent wasn't
可能那个代理人不是
winning the auction before in which case
在这种情况下赢得拍卖
the social welfare maximizing outcome
社会福利最大化成果
remains the same
保持原样
agent has been dropped and nothing
代理已删除，什么也没有
changes and so then I get equality in
变化，然后我得到平等
this expression or that is the agent who
这个表达或那个代理是谁
was winning before and then I pick a
之前赢了，然后我选择了
different winner once that agent has
该代理拥有不同的获胜者
been dropped
被丢弃
I'll get less social welfare overall
我的整体社会福利会减少
which is why I was picking a different
这就是为什么我选择不同的原因
agent in the first place but when I
首先是代理商，但当我
consider only agents other than I
只考虑我以外的代理商
they're all going to be happier when I
当我的时候他们都会更快乐
has been dropped than when I was present
比我在场的时候掉了
because one of them gets to win after I
因为其中之一在我之后获胜
was dropped and in the case where I was
被丢弃，如果我是
president one of them wasn't winning so
总统其中一位没有赢
you can see it's kind of actually a
你可以看到它实际上是一个
pretty natural property this ain't no
很自然的属性这不是
single agent effect so turns out that
单剂效应，结果证明
this is all we need to prove that VCG is
这就是我们需要证明VCG是
weekly budget balanced and indeed it's a
每周预算平衡，实际上是
pretty direct proof so as before let's
像以前一样非常直接的证明
assume truth-telling an equilibrium and
假设说实话的均衡，
now what we want to think about is the
现在我们要考虑的是
sum of transfers that agents make to the
代理商向客户转移的总和
center so the sum of all of the payments
中心，所以所有付款的总和
and I want to show that the sum of all
我想证明所有的总和
of these payments is greater than or
这些付款中的大于或
equal to zero that's going to mean week
等于零意味着一周
budget balance so once again this is the
预算余额，所以这又是
VCG payment function and now I'm just
VCG支付功能，现在我只是
summing the payment function across all
汇总所有支付功能
of the agents because I'm interested in
的代理商，因为我对
the aggregate payment from the no single
单笔付款的总和
agent effect condition I know that for
我知道代理作用条件
all of the agents other than I the value
除我以外的所有代理商的价值
they have for a world for the choice
他们有选择的世界
that gets made when I is dropped the
当我掉下来的时候
social welfare maximizing choice for
社会福利最大化的选择
them that gets made when I is dropped is
当我掉下来的时候，它们是
at least as big as the sum over all of
至少等于全部
their utilities for the choice that gets
他们的实用程序，以获得选择
made when I is not dropped
当我不落水时
that's just directly what no single
那就是直接没有任何一个
agent effect means and you can see that
代理效应意味着，您可以看到
these are exactly the terms that I have
这些正是我所拥有的术语
in the VCG payment function
在VCG付款功能中
and so the result follows directly this
所以结果直接跟随这个
blue term is bigger than the green term
蓝色项大于绿色项
which means that this expression up here
这意味着这里的表达
is just positive for every eye and not
对每一只眼睛都是正面的，而不是
negative for every eye and so that gives
对每只眼睛都是负面的
us what we want which is that this whole
我们我们想要的是那整个
sum is greater than or equal to zero
总和大于或等于零
well I have one last bit of good news to
好吧，我还有最后一个好消息要
give you here's a theorem from Krishna
给你一个来自克里希纳的定理
and peri which says something else about
和peri，这还说了一些关于
the revenue and VCG which is even more
收入和VCG甚至更多
encouraging than we just saw it says
比我们刚刚看到的鼓舞人心的
consider any Bayesian game setting in
考虑任何贝叶斯游戏设置
which VCG is ex-post individually
哪个VCG是单独邮寄的
rational and the claim is that in such
理性的主张是
as case VCG collects at least as much
如果VCG至少收集了
revenue as any other efficient and X
收益与其他任何有效收益和X
interim individually rational mechanism
临时个体理性机制
now here are a couple of things to kind
现在这里有几件好事
of walk through about what what is being
逐步了解正在发生什么
claimed here first of all you might
首先要在这里声明
wonder about this little preamble didn't
奇怪这个序言没有
we already talk about what happens when
我们已经在谈论什么时候会发生什么
VCG is ex-post individual rational well
VCG是事后个人理性的好
not really because what we looked at
并不是真的因为我们看了什么
before was two conditions that are
之前有两个条件
sufficient for VCG to be individual
足以使VCG变得个性化
rational we didn't claim that there
理性的，我们没有声称那里
aren't other things that might be true
不是其他事情可能是真的
about the setting that would also result
关于也会导致的设置
in VCG being individual rational so what
在VCG中是个人理性，那么
this theorem says is don't worry about
这个定理说不用担心
how you got there think about any
你怎么到那里想什么
setting in which VCG is ex-post
后期VCG的设置
individual rational it'll include what
个人理性将包括什么
we talked about before but it'll include
我们之前讨论过，但其中包括
other settings too and what it says is
其他设置也是如此
VCG collects at least as much revenue as
VCG收集的收入至少与
any other efficient mechanism a thing to
任何其他有效的机制
notice here is even if that mechanism
注意，即使该机制
only uses Bayes Nash equilibrium we're
只使用贝叶斯纳什均衡
not assuming that this other mechanism
不假设其他机制
is dominant-strategy efficient so this
是有效的主导策略，所以这
other mechanism gets to be drawn from a
其他机制必须从
much bigger pool the dominant strategy
更大的池占主导地位的策略
mechanisms and the Bayes Nash
机制和贝叶斯纳什
equilibrium mechanisms and another sense
平衡机制和另一种意义
in which it's drawn from a bigger pool
从更大的水池中抽出来的
is that we're only going to require of
是我们只需要
this competitor mechanism that it's X
这就是X的竞争机制
interim individual rational whereas
临时个人理性而
we're requiring a VCG that it's ex-post
我们需要事后的VCG
individual
个人
so this is a X syndrome individual
这是一个X综合征个体
rationality is a weaker thing to require
理性是一个较弱的要求
which means there's a broader set of
这意味着有更广泛的
mechanisms that would satisfy it which
满足它的机制
means that we're making a stronger
意味着我们正在变得更强大
statement when we compare VCG to this
我们将VCG与之比较的声明
broad set so a way of understanding this
广泛设置，这样一种理解这一点的方式
result is that VC G is as budget
结果是VC G作为预算
balanced as any efficient mechanism can
任何有效机制都可以平衡
be so I'm not saying here necessarily
是的，所以我不必在这里说
that the revenue is greater than or
收入大于或
equal to zero sometimes it will be and
等于零，有时会是
sometimes not but in cases where the
有时不是，但在
revenue is still none a still negative
收入仍然没有负数
what this result says is if VCG was
这个结果说明的是如果VCG是
ex-post individual rational there's no
事后个人理性没有
other mechanism which is efficient and
其他有效的机制
which gets more revenue so VC G is
它获得了更多收入，所以VC G是
always getting as close to budget
总是接近预算
balance as efficient mechanisms can as
平衡，因为有效的机制可以
long as vc g remains individually
只要vc g保持单独
rational
合理的